[
  {
    "question": "I _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "am",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["is", "are", "me"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["Dave", "Sam", "Dean", "Eric", "Victor", "Nate", "Chuck", "Dan", "Kevin", "Tom", "Mike", "Tim", "Stan", "Peter", "Damon", "Steve", "Betty", "Veronica", "Kate", "Blair", "Serena", "Vanessa", "Margo", "Bella", "Alice", "Stella", "Penny", "Erica", "Ann", "Carla", "Maria", "Lizzy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["are", "am", "iz"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["Dave", "Sam", "Dean", "Eric", "Victor", "Nate", "Chuck", "Dan", "Kevin", "Tom", "Mike", "Tim", "Stan", "Peter", "Damon", "Steve"]
  },
  {
    "question": "She _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["am", "are", "ise"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["Betty", "Veronica", "Kate", "Blair", "Serena", "Vanessa", "Margo", "Bella", "Alice", "Stella", "Penny", "Erica", "Ann", "Carla", "Maria", "Lizzy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "am",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["are", "is", "my"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["two years old", "three years old", "four years old", "five years old", "six years old", "seven years old", "eight years old", "nine years old", "ten years old", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "She _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["am", "are", "ar"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["two years old", "three years old", "four years old", "five years old", "six years old", "seven years old", "eight years old", "nine years old", "ten years old", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["are", "am", "iz"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["two years old", "three years old", "four years old", "five years old", "six years old", "seven years old", "eight years old", "nine years old", "ten years old", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It _____ a * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["are", "am", "its"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "fox", "bear", "wolf", "lion", "giraffe", "monkey", "banana", "moon", "star", "heart", "square", "triangle", "circle", "cloud", "hat", "scarf", "cucumber", "tomato", "potato", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ it a * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "Is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Am", "Are", "Iz"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "fox", "bear", "wolf", "lion", "giraffe", "monkey", "banana", "moon", "star", "heart", "square", "triangle", "circle", "cloud", "hat", "scarf", "cucumber", "tomato", "potato", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I _____ from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "am",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["are", "is", "my"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "She _____ from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["am", "are", "it"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He _____ from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["are", "am", "ise"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We _____ from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "are",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["is", "am", "ar"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You _____ from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "are",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["is", "am", "arre"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "They _____ from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "are",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["am", "is", "ar"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ they from * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "Are",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Is", "Am", "Aer"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "These _____ my * .",
    "correctAnswer": "are",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["is", "am", "arre"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ these my * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "Are",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Am", "Is", "Aar"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  }
]